[{"QuizTitle":"Quiz MVC","quiz_questions":[{"data_questions":[{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":100,"QuestionText":"The controller redirects incoming request to model.","Correct":true},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":200,"QuestionText":"The controller executes an incoming request.","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":300,"QuestionText":"The controller controls the data.","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":400,"QuestionText":"The controller render html to view.","Correct":false}],"HeaderIndex":1,"HeaderText":"Which of following is TRUE?"},{"data_questions":[{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":100,"QuestionText":"Model, View \u0026 Controller","Correct":true},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":200,"QuestionText":"Model, Vision \u0026 Control","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":300,"QuestionText":"Model, ViewData \u0026 Controller","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":400,"QuestionText":"Model, Data \u0026 Controller","Correct":false}],"HeaderIndex":2,"HeaderText":"MVC stands for ______."},{"data_questions":[{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":100,"QuestionText":"@Component","Correct":true},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":200,"QuestionText":"@Controller","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":300,"QuestionText":"@RestService","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":400,"QuestionText":"@MVCController","Correct":false}],"HeaderIndex":3,"HeaderText":"Which annotation is used to define a controller in Spring MVC?"},{"data_questions":[{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":100,"QuestionText":"Display","Correct":true},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":200,"QuestionText":"Show","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":300,"QuestionText":"View","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":400,"QuestionText":"Render","Correct":false}],"HeaderIndex":4,"HeaderText":"Which method in a controller returns a View in ASP.NET Core MVC?"},{"data_questions":[{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":100,"QuestionText":"app.route()","Correct":true},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":200,"QuestionText":"app.get()","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":300,"QuestionText":"express.get()","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":400,"QuestionText":"router.create()","Correct":false}],"HeaderIndex":5,"HeaderText":"Which method is used to define a GET route in Express?"},{"data_questions":[{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":100,"QuestionText":"Code","Correct":true},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":200,"QuestionText":"Controller","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":300,"QuestionText":"Class","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":400,"QuestionText":"Content","Correct":false}],"HeaderIndex":6,"HeaderText":"In MVC architecture, what does the \u0027C\u0027 stand for?"},{"data_questions":[{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":100,"QuestionText":"Model","Correct":true},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":200,"QuestionText":"View","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":300,"QuestionText":"Controller","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":400,"QuestionText":"Template","Correct":false}],"HeaderIndex":7,"HeaderText":"Which part of MVC is responsible for handling user input?"}]},{"QuizTitle":"Quiz JS","quiz_questions":[{"data_questions":[{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":100,"QuestionText":"yes","Correct":true},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":200,"QuestionText":"No","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":300,"QuestionText":"maybe","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":400,"QuestionText":":)","Correct":false}],"HeaderIndex":1,"HeaderText":"Do you have any plans to add design Pattern , Context concept"},{"data_questions":[{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":100,"QuestionText":"\u002B\u002B\u002B learn by writing code","Correct":true},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":200,"QuestionText":"- outdated","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":300,"QuestionText":"- not comprehensive","Correct":false},{"Answer":false,"AnswerLetter":0,"Letter":400,"QuestionText":"- not very good explaining async fundamentals","Correct":false}],"HeaderIndex":2,"HeaderText":"w3schools is..."}]}]